<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
<ServerGroup Name="CLASSIC Style HARDCORE" Logo="https://i.imgur.com/8duWP6I.jpg"> <!-- Logo is a direct link to a jpg /png file. Default image dimension is 2064x452 -->
<Server Name="Classic Style Hardcore">
<!-- This forces the mod launcher to make a copy of the game for the mod. 
	Mod that use BepInEx, and relative paths should use this setting.
	Remove Deploy or change it to Partial to skip that step	-->
<!-- This is the alpha version you last tested with -->
<!-- You can use Latest if you just want the current one -->
<Version>alpha21.2</Version>
<DownloadMode>Release</DownloadMode>
<!-- Only the first download is used -->
<Downloads>
	<Download>https://github.com/n2n1/Classic-Style-Hardcore-MOD/releases</Download>
	<AltDownload></AltDownload>
</Downloads>
	
<!-- Got a website -->
<WebSite>https://community.7daystodie.com/topic/22253-classic-style-hardcore/</WebSite>

<Description>Mod version: CSH v21.2.05hf (test)

Date: 24.11.2023

Requiring Alpha: 21.2(b30)

Size in archive: ~ 700Mb



РУС:
(про дополнительные возможности, совместимость сейвов, изменения в версии - читаем на оффициальном форуме)
ENG:
(read about save compatibility, changes, and extensions - in the forums)
日本:
日本語訳作成： ちびにゃ, はぴろう, ひろけーえぬえぬ
(追加機能、保存の互換性、バージョンの変更について - 公式フォーラムで読む)


********************************************************************************************************************

TERMS of USE modification(mod) "CLASSIC Style HARDCORE" based on the game "7 Days to Die":

1. Content created by the author of the mod or third parties, which NOT based on the developments of "The Fun Pimps" - belongs to the creators of this content.
2. The terms below do not apply to the owners of the game "The Fun Pimps", as they already have the right to use their own content or code, including those that were created on the basis of their development. The author of this mod does not mind that "The Fun Pimps" use any ideas or materials from this mod to improve the quality of the game "7 Days to Die".
3. You can use the mod, change or take any of the content for personal use outside of the public - without permission.
4. You can use the mod without changes (as is) on public servers for non-commercial purposes or show the gameplay - without permission.
5. To use the mod in public, or create a public server with changes in the configuration files xml, txt, dll or other resources - you must ask the author of the mod for permission.
6. If you want to publicly use any materials or content from this mod outside of this mod, you must ask the author of the mod for permission.
</Description>




<!-- Who made -->
<Author>n2n1</Author>

<!-- Have a discord you want people to join? -->
<Discord></Discord>

<!-- Want to give people an option to donate? -->
<Donate></Donate>

<!-- Got some release notes you want people to view? -->
<ReleaseNotes></ReleaseNotes>

	<RSS/>

</Server>
</ServerGroup>
</Servers>